

Kadir Salvarcioglu

Contact

Address Allschwilerstrasse 112

4055 Basel

Phone +41 77 204 72 63

E-Mail <u>kadir.salvarci@gmail.com</u>

GitHub | WebPage | Linkedin

Personal Information

Birth date Civil 12.12.1983

Status Married

Nationality Turkish (Permit B)

Hobbies Writing code, Foot-

ball, Travelling, Watching Movie, Photography

<u>Languages</u>

Türkisch

Muttersprache

Deutsch

Telc Zertifikat B1

Englisch

ر و

Reference

Anastasia- Viola Pantazakos Tel.: +41 61 267 58 20 Viola.pantazakos@bs.ch

SUMMARY

Bachelor of Business Administration and more than seven years in the workforce. A true team player with strong collaboration skills and a mindset that is always trying to find best practice development, he is now looking for a career change position in IT. More than two years of Hands-on training in DevOps and AWS. Hands-on training in designing and building effective Continuous Integration and Delivery (CI/CD) pipelines using containeri- zation, orchestration, monitoring, infrastructure automation tools, configuration manage- ment tools, and AWS solutions. Ability to use Jira as a project management tool and agile methodology as a project management method.

IT SKİLLS

- Advanced: HTML, CSS, Git/Github ,Terraform
- Intermediate: AWS, SQL, Agile (Scrum), Docker, Kubernetes
- Beginner: JavaScript, Python, Selenium, Ansible, Jira
- Terraform HashiCorp Certified: Terraform Associate (003)

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2023 - Centrepoint Basel (Switzerland)

Volunteer (IT and calendar coordinator)

03/2021 – 07/2021 Basel Brocki Second Hand Store (Switzerland)

• Volunteer employment program

03/2011 - 01/2017 Police Officer, Ministry of Interior(Turkey)

• Various programs and systems of the Turkish Police Department

01/2009 – 12/2009 Restaurant manager assistant(Turkey)

Restaurant management

09/2007 - 12/2008 Primary School Teacher (Turkey)

• Math and Turkish teach.

LIFE EXPERIENCE

01/2017 - 01/2021 Political problems in Turkey and country change

12/2009 - 06/2010 Compulsory Military (Turkey)

EDUCATION / CONTINUOUS EDUCATION

01/2023 - 05/23 Terraform (official certificate)

10/2022 –12/2022 Docker: Build PortfolioSite (Coursera)

10/2022 - 12/2022 SQL (Coursera)

08/2022 – 11/2022 AWS Fundam.: Migrating to the Cloud (Coursera)

04/2022 - 06/2022 HTML5, University of Michigan (Coursera)

05/2022 - 06/2022 HTML, CSS, JS for Web Developers IBM (Coursera)

04/2022 - 06/2022 Swisscom - NGG Academy, Zurich (Switzerland)

• Foundations in HTML, CSS, JavaScript; specialization tracks upcoming Weekly business & social skills training (team work, communication, etc.)

05/2020 -03/2021 CLARUSWAY - AWS&DevOps Engineer Course (USA-ONLINE)

 Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, Linux, Git, GitHub, Cloud (AWS), Docker, Kubernetes, Jira, Slack, Ansible, Terraform, Scrum/Kanban, Selenium

07/2010 - 01/2011 Turkish Police School (Turkey)

09/2002 - 07/2007 Konya Selcuk University (Turkey)

• School of Business Administration